Rebeca Chavez Villa

San Diego, CA 92154 rebecachavez99_9bq@indeedemail.com 858-345-0204

Dynamic, energetic and highly experienced over 14 years in commercial and community property management with a solid history of success Steadfast leader, mentor and coordinator with track record of steering improvement projects, building and guiding top-performing teams and optimizing internal operations. Talent for cultivating and supporting relationships. I am motivated, disciplined, focused and determined to get the job well and on time. Strong attention to detail, organizational, and time management skills

Strong understanding of accounting principles and procedure. Experienced in handling book-keeping activities and fixing accounting errors. Experienced in accounts payable, account receivable, and processing invoice payment. Ability to work with integrated accounting financial software and reporting system. very strong work ethic and dedicated to my work. I'm a multi task person, with excellent communication and interpersonal skills, computer skills (Windows Vista/XP, MS Word, MS Excel, MS PowerPoint, Access, Outlook, QuickBooks) and CRM, with organization, speed and accuracy.

#readytowork

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Quality Control Assistant

Go-Staff,Inc. - San Diego, CA September 2019 to Present

Staffing Agency with over 15 years of experience in San Diego, California

- Excellent at reading and interpreting complex instructions
- Responsible for collecting all quality control information throughout the week and developing a week-ending report for management.
- Strong eye for detail
- Exceptional communication and presentation skills
- Responsible for doing quality control audits daily, weekly and monthly month and creating reports for management .

Real Estate Agent

DECASA

February 2016 to 2019

Rosarito Beach Mexico

Developer Company with more than 35 years building high-end tourist developments in the city of Rosarito.

- Worked as a Selling / Buyer Agent Customer Relations: Nurtured healthy customer relationship to ensure timely payments.
- Arranged and attended multiple showings of properties
- Drafted and completed contracts
- Developed marketing strategies for real estate listings
- Interviewed clients to determine what kinds of properties they were seeking and generat- ed lists, meeting those requirements from available properties
- Accompanied clients during visits and inspections of desired properties; advised them on value of the property, current market value and market trends
- Pitched leads through cold calls using company database programs; following up on these leads via face-to-face meetings, telephone and/or emails

HR Supervisor

Real Estate Office, Rosario Beach - MX 2009 to 2012

Mexico

- Assisted in the development and implementation of personnel policies and procedures; participated in developing department goals, objectives and systems.
- Prepared and translated legal documents including listings and buy/sales contracts.
- Project manager.
- Supervised external collaborators
- Responsible of following up on sales revenue, bank reconciliations, petty cash control, etc.
- Prepared necessary paperwork and administered all invoices on spreadsheet and maintain records of all documents
- CRM Program management
- Pitched leads through cold calls using company database programs; following up on these leads via face-to-face meetings, telephone and/or emails

Accounting administrative Manager

Consultores Profesionales 1985 to 2008

Tijuana B.C. Mexico

Partner at a family business accounting office for over twenty three years, my main function was as an office manager.

- Provided high-level administrative support and managed organizational policies and pro- cedures.
- Managed Accounts Payable/Receivable and expense-control procedures, including bank and account reconciliation, cash receipts, disbursements, finance, charge, billings, invoic- ing, purchase order and inventory verification, chargebacks, rebate, and preparation of daily bank deposits.
- · Recruited and managed staff, including hiring and development assessments to staff.
- Liaison between employees and clients to ensure proper lines of communication critical in addressing myriad problems and issues requiring immediate attention and resolve.
- Collaborated extensively with auditors, providing in-depht assistance with audits.

Cost Accountant Assistant

Optimex S.A - Tijuana, MX

1980 to 1984

Mexico

Cost Accounting Clerk (Bilingual)

Detail-oriented Manufacturing Cost Accountant Clerk specializing in generally accepted ac- counting principles applicable to manufacturing costs including revenue and expenditures.

Education

Associate in Accounting

UABC. Tijuana , Mexico - Tijuana, Mexico September 1978 to November 1979

Skills

- Reconciliation (10+ years)
- Journal (10+ years)
- GI (10+ years)
- Accounts receivable (5 years)
- Data analyst (5 years)
- Database
- Billing (5 years)
- Collections
- Quickbooks (2 years)
- Excel (10+ years)
- Outlook (5 years)
- Ms powerpoint (3 years)
- Powerpoint
- Ms word (10+ years)
- Word
- Windows vista (10+ years)
- Detail oriented (10+ years)
- Excellent communication skills (5 years)
- Excellent multi-tasker (10+ years)
- Multi-tasker (10+ years)
- Real Estate (5 years)
- Hiring (10+ years)
- Quality Control (Less than 1 year)
- CAPA (Corrective and preventing Actions) System Procedures (Less than 1 year)
- Avionte (Recruiting and Staffing Software) (Less than 1 year)

Certifications and Licenses

ISO 9000

Present

Reliability — Highly Proficient

January 2020

Tendency to be dependable and come to work.
Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/

share_to_profile/50c4cb7f51a5ffc4ee9efe8ffed553f5eed53dc074545cb7

Project Management Skills: Time Management — Proficient

December 2019

Prioritizing and allocating time to effectively achieve project deliverables. Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/share_to_profile/

e021f976a6fcd40b32ae6279dfcb7f19eed53dc074545cb7

Organizational Skills — Proficient

February 2020

Arranging and managing information or materials using a set of rules.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/

share_to_profile/5a2ce52d397f69ca7e883830f6ec0235eed53dc074545cb7

Manufacturing: Quality Inspection — Proficient

February 2020

Making precise measurements, reading prints, and making pass/fail decisions.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/

share to profile/8d6d5510da1925531883af22f604c04feed53dc074545cb7

Spreadsheets with Microsoft Excel — Proficient

February 2020

Excel knowledge including common tools, PivotTables, conditional & nested formulas, and custom visuals.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/attempts/ e3303d209d6a7bade3a3cf55cfde34c0eed53dc074545cb7

Supervisory Skills: Motivating & Assessing Employees — Highly Proficient

February 2020

Motivating others to achieve objectives and identifying improvements or corrective actions.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/

attempts/9a7de0c6979aee9c13f2bae2809a459aeed53dc074545cb7

Management & Leadership Skills: Impact & Influence — Highly Proficient

February 2020

Adapting leadership style to accomplish goals using rational or emotional appeal.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/attempts/ f73d27e8fe7006278c4098203032ef6aeed53dc074545cb7

Principles of Accounting — Proficient

March 2020

Preparing financial records according to federal policies.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/

share_to_profile/8ff9621fcd119168d4bd1403f6337f5deed53dc074545cb7

Working with MS Word Documents — Highly Proficient

March 2020

Knowledge of various Microsoft Word features, functions, and techniques.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/share_to_profile/

cf0333b5e8edcf948943e58c65132fcfeed53dc074545cb7

Work Style: Reliability — Highly Proficient

February 2020

Tendency to be dependable and come to work.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/share to profile/

 $\underline{d33c175e0ba60a0b86edd173b353fb1deed53dc074545cb7}$

Accounting Skills: Bookkeeping — Highly Proficient

April 2020

Calculating and determining the accuracy of financial data.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/

share to profile/97168d11c25d9e9cef36e3f7d26bb427eed53dc074545cb7

Attention to Detail — Completed

February 2020

Identifying differences in materials, following instructions, and detecting details among distracting information.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/

share to profile/0c05575373c453de1bf7db42527e656beed53dc074545cb7

Principles of Accounting — Proficient

March 2020

Preparing financial records according to federal policies.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/attempts/b58b1e96b2a737230a241e7f9379184deed53dc074545cb7

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.

Additional Information

SKILLS

- Excellent multi-tasker and negotiation Detail oriented
- Staff development & training GL Reconciliation
- Proficient windows vista/xp, ms word, ms Spreadsheet and database creation

excel, ms powerpoint, access, outlook, • Spreadsheets & Journal Entries

QuickBooks • Data analyst

- Financial Records & Reporting Staff development & training
- Billing & Collections Goal-oriented
- Excellent communication skills
- Accounts Receivable
- Client and vendor relations
- Outstanding people skills
- CAPA Corrective and Preventing Actions) System Procedures
- Avionte (Recruiting and Staffing software)